Carol Wiessner

® 770.568.8832 ☑ carolw30004@yahoo.com △ Metro Atlanta, GA 🚱 linkedin.com/in/carol-w-atlanta

February 1, 2018

Omni International, Inc. 935 Cobb Place Blvd. NW Kennesaw, GA 30144

Job Ref #: 12334

Dear Mr. Masefield,

I am excited to be reaching out you today. Omni International's position for *Marketing Assistant* aligns perfectly with my experience and training. I have pursued an increasingly successful career, supporting both internal and external clients, in addition to vendors and staff within marketing services.

My thirst for continued development has allowed my career to evolve over the years. I am a proven professional adept at prioritizing and completing multiple assignments within strict budgetary/time restrictions and corporate specifications.

I am a successful communicator at all levels with exceptional interpersonal and organizational skills. I am able to recognize, act upon, and coordinate complex logistics, bringing strategic planning and vision toward current goals and future growth. Below are two outstanding accomplishments.

- Collaborating with sales and marketing, which was subsequently adopted for implementation, I recommended the company provide a "free look" for their highly interactive courses enabling email address capture, subsequently enabling greater potential for enrollment increases.
- Analyzing sales and enrollments within India member companies, I recommended eliminating regional pricing and special inventory, which reduce expenses \$30,000 in the first year.

I would be honored if you find my résumé intriguing enough to request a formal meeting to view my portfolio and discuss in-depth how my qualifications would be an asset to the Omni International family. I can be reached via mobile and text at 770-568-8832. Thank you for your time and consideration.

Sincerely,

Carol Wiessner

Encl: Resume

Carol Wiessner

® 770.568.8832 ☑ carolw30004@yahoo.com △ Metro Atlanta, GA 🚱 linkedin.com/in/carol-w-atlanta

Summary

Dedicated **marketing services professional** within corporate, agency and manufacturing environments. 10+ years in purchasing, logistics, inventory, product design and production management. Computer savvy, analytical and strategic thinker that identifies customer needs, and anticipates outcomes, providing recommendations for process improvements that drives efficiency and profitability Extensive experience in:

- Purchasing and contract management
- Vendor management and negotiations
- Logistics and supply chain management
- Customer liaison and support

- Accounting and financial reporting
- Project/Product management
- Policy and procedure development
- Improving productivity and efficiency

Professional Experience

LL Global, Inc. dba LOMA, Atlanta, Georgia

2006-2016

LOMA provides education courses to the insurance and financial services industry in nine languages for the more than 40,000 individuals who enroll each year for over 70,000 courses and examinations worldwide.

Operations Manager, Education and Training Division, 2014-2016

Managed the centralized and shared operational services including, product distribution, inventory, publishing support, vendor relations, intellectual property, contract and financial operations. Directed a wide variety of projects and strategic initiatives, collaborated with internal departments to develop operating strategies, maximize efficiency and improve the customer experience.

Contributions:

- Successfully developed and implemented the organization's contract process in SharePoint, streamlining assembly, tracking, storage and ensuring contractual compliance, increasing executed agreements by 40% in 12 months.
- Improved international paper exam schedule by consolidating several documents thereby reducing confusion, errors and improving cross-functional communication.
- Led the orchestration and implementation of the company relocation for the division. Successful choreography resulted in staff being productive within 4 hours on the first day.

Product Sourcing Manager, Education and Training Division, 2006-2014

Managed purchasing, logistics and supply chain of 300+ educational products produced in six languages and generating \$3 million in revenue. Established and maintained critical business relationships with key print and media vendors, publishers and domestic and international distributors to ensure availability to customers worldwide.

Contributions:

- Designed and developed automated online order forms (PDF, JavaScript enabled) improving order accuracy and eliminating print and inventory expense.
- Spearheaded the implementation of online publication protection software in seven languages. Presided over business units in developing of policy and processes. Oversaw end-to-end development/testing, conducted system training and created support documentation.
- Reduced purchasing cost by 10% by introducing standard branding guidelines for publications.

Carol Wiessner

🕾 770.568.8832 🖂 carolw30004@yahoo.com 🗅 Metro Atlanta, GA 🚱 linkedin.com/in/carol-w-atlanta

Page 2

Additional Professional Experience:

- Coordinated all activities related to the production of cable affiliate kits, retail and channel-programming
 promotional (POP) materials for a top broadcasting company. Collaborated with creative, marketing and media
 sales teams, to create and produce desired products on-time and within budget.
- Served as Direct Mail Production Specialist for a major auto manufacturer's insurance division, completing one million mailings per week consisting of 4-5 co-op clients.
- Managed 150 marketing items and a \$1.5 million inventory for a \$2 billion real estate investment company.
 Purchased and coordinated monthly print, promotional items, transcripts, and mailings on time and with 99.5% quality accuracy.
- Increase print profits by 30% in twelve months by creating cost-effective marketing programs with vendors, and providing education to designers in economical print and mailing methods.

Technical Skills

- Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook, Access
- InDesign, Illustrator, Photoshop, Acrobat
- SharePoint, Onyx CRM, Vitrium DRM
- QlikView, Meridian System
- Survey Monkey, Social Media Apps
- PC and Mac Platforms

Education/Training/Career Enrichment

- Business Administration, Saint Joseph Academy, Ohio
- Intellectual Property Law & Policy: Copyright and Trademark, University of Pennsylvania
- An Introduction to American Law, University of Pennsylvania
- LOMA Designations: ALMI (Associate, Life Management Institute); AIRC (Associate, Insurance Regulatory Compliance); AIAA (Associate, Insurance Agency Administration); ACS (Associate, Customer Service)
- Legal Aspects of Purchasing, Nahabit & Associates, Leslie S. Marell, J.D.
- Contracts: Reading, Writing and Negotiating, Nahabit & Associates, Leslie S. Marell, J.D.